# Jordan Willian Marques Pereira

Computer Engineer

Website: https://jordanwmp.github.io

Applications in Play Store

Projects in the GitHub

Whatsapp: +55 (98) 9 8718-0471

Email: jordanwillian.ecp@gmail.com

Location: Sao Luís, MA, Brazil - Available for national/international relocation.

#### **Professional Profile:**

I have a degree in Computer Engineering and I intend to build a solid career as a Software Engineer and Architect, with an emphasis on Front-End and Mobile development, through hybrid technologies. My work is focused on the JavaScript ecosystem, exploring its versatility for the development of APIs, mobile applications and web platforms.

I seek to integrate the theoretical foundations of computing with practical challenges, maintaining a continuous learning routine, through studies, reading and specialized courses, constantly improving my skills as a Computer Engineer.

#### **Technical Skills:**

Algorithms, Software Engineering, Software Architecture, Scrum, Javascript, TypeScript, Angular, Vue.js, React, React Native, Expo, Ionic Framework, Capacitor, Node.js, API, Sequelize, Prisma, RxJS, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Pinia, Jest, Jasmine, Webpack, PWA, Git, HTML, CSS, Tailwind, SASS, Bootstrap, Angular Material, Firebase, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, MySQL, Redis, Play Console, Google Cloud, Trello, Google Admob, RevenueCat, Gather Town.

# **Professional Experience:**

## Academia Noby | Freelancer | 2023 - 2024

• Typescript, Angular, Ionic Framework, Node.js, Firebase, API Rest.

# **Dutra University Hospital | Internship | 2023 - 2023**

• HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Laravel, PostgreSQL

## Exact Engineering | Freelancer | Mobile | 2022

Typescript, Angular, Ionic Framework, Firebase

## Sousândrade Foundation | Scientific Research | 2020 - 2021

IoT, Embedded Systems, C, Ionic Framework, Angular, Typescript

# Adsum | Software Engineering | 2019 - 2020

Software Engineering, Requirements Analysis, Angular, Ionic Framework,
Scrum, MySQL, Laravel, PHP, Javascript, Typescript, Firebase.

# Adsum | Internship | 2018 - 2019

• Python, PHP, Ionic Framework, Angular, Laravel, MySQL, Firebase.

# **Academic Background:**

Computer Engineering: UFMA, Nov. 2024

Science and Technology: UFMA, Sept. 2019

# Languages:

English: Level B2

Portuguese: Native

#### **Complementary Activities:**

- I participated in digital transformation projects at the Federal University of Maranhão
- I taught a Data Science course at <u>National Oceanography Week</u> for Physical Oceanography.

## Personal project:

I developed the RDO Digital mobile application for construction project management. The application aims to increase efficiency in project control, centralizing information and issuing reports on the same. The RDO Digital can be found at <a href="website">website</a> or in <a href="Play Store">Play Store</a>.